Kat, I'm trying to think, is there like an analogy of liberals invading, I mean, Republicans invading like a liberal bastion and saying, if we just hang out here, you know what I mean?
It feels like they're poaching, they're trying to poach people, but it's not working.
Yeah, I don't feel like Democrats need to go to the gym.
I think they just need to go somewhere.
Right.
Right?
Like, I don't feel like it should be that complicated.
Yeah, you're right.
Instead of maybe sitting around, like, running analytics on men, why don't you just go out and meet them?
Right.
Like, they're not like mythical creatures in a forest.
You can just go talk to dudes.
Yes.
It's not that hard.
You don't have to.
It's actually too easy.
Yeah, it is.
It's harder to not talk to dudes than it is to talk to dudes.
Just unbutton the top button.
It works for me.
But they're acting like you need to, like, create men in a laboratory and then, like, run tests on them.
Just go outside.
Go to a place where people are.
But you have to talk and you also have to listen.
You have to listen without looking for a thing where it's like, well, actually, this thing you set.
You have to just listen.
Yeah.
But you know what?
You're saying it's easy to go outside.
But that might be the number one issue is that they don't like going outside in general.
Well, who does?
Yeah, that's true.
I don't know.
Yeah.